My Cart 

Your cart is empty!

Subtotal $0.00

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Statement  
  
\----  
  
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?  
  
When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.  
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.  
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.  
  
SECTION 2 - CONSENT  
  
How do you get my consent?  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.  
  
How do I withdraw my consent?  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at contact@pureratios.com or by calling us at 619-955-1339.  
  
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE  
  
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.  
  
SECTION 4 - SHOPIFY  
  
Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.  
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.  
  
Payment:  
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.  
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.  
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.  
For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).  
  
SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES  
  
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.  
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.  
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.  
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.  
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.  
  
Links  
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.  

SECTION 6 - SECURITY  
  
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.  
  
SECTION 7 - COOKIES  
  
Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
\_session\_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).  
\_shopify\_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits  
\_shopify\_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.  
cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.  
\_secure\_session\_id, unique token, sessional  
storefront\_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.  

SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT  
  
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.  
  
SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.  
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION  
  
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at contact@pureratios.com or by calling us at 619-821-2997.

* * *

Call us at: [619.821.2997](tel:6198212997)

Email us at: [contact@pureratios.com](mailto:contact@pureratios.com)

### DISCLOSURE:

The statements made regarding these products have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. The efficacy of these products has not been confirmed by FDA-approved research. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. All information presented here is not meant as a substitute for or alternative to information from health care practitioners. Please consult your health care professional about potential interactions or other possible complications before using any product. The Federal Food, Drug and Cosmetic Act requires this notice. Please consult your health care provider before making any healthcare decisions or for guidance about a specific medical condition. Pure Ratios shall have no liability for any damages, loss, injury or liability whatsoever suffered as a result of your reliance on the information contained in this site. We are unable to ship Hemp Extract products to the following states: Idaho, Iowa, South Dakota and Nebraska. Return Policy: Once order has been received you have 30 days to return, unopened packages only. Any manufacturer defects or issues on the part of the manufacturer, you may return for a replacement or refund within 30 days of purchase. Pricing and specials are subject to change. Please be aware that the products may contain essential oils and infused herbs, therefore if you have any allergies to such please do not use. 

©2022 Pure Ratios. All Rights Reserved.

### Age Verification

You must be 21+ years old to access this site.
